# 10003a5b.txt
#
# Copyright (c) 2007 Symbian Software Ltd. All rights reserved.
#
# Repository initialisation file for agnmodel
#

cenrep
version 1

#[owner] - Who is responsible for back up

[platsec]
# Default capabilities for folder repository
cap_rd=ReadUserData cap_wr=AllFiles, WriteDeviceData

[main]
# 100 - The data key
# int - The data type
# 1 - The value. When it is "1", alarms in the past due to system time change will be notified.
# Change it to "0" if you don't want alarms in the past to be notified. 
# 0 - The data mask
 
100	int	1	0


